[{"answer": "I have a friend coming in from out of town, I'll probably be spending some time with him the next couple of days", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Right", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "my friend, I don't think you want to, I mean, you should see the way he dresses. I really think he's in a bad way", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "You're intrigued", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "How long has it been since you've seen my friend", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Nine years", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " my friend, father, sister", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Younger", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I'm sorry. Am I prying again", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Yes, this afternoon. I was grilling my friend about your marriage this afternoon", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I say it because it's descriptive", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I have a pretty good idea", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "He doesn't have a phone", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Let me talk to him first", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I don't feel right just giving you the address so that you can go over there and..", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "That goddam diamond stud earring that cost me a fucking fortune", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I don't know, I'll get her a card or something", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "What brought this on", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " I thought that's what I did. Who was it that you talked to", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "It's a personal project I'm working on", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Oh, just a personal project like anyone else's personal project. Mine's just a little more personal", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Oh, just a personal project like anyone else's personal project. Mine's just a little more personal", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "What...what are these interviews about", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "About sex", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Everything about sex", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "How about inviting me over to dinner", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Yeah, I know what you mean", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I, uh, know a guy at the power company", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Well, I don't really listen to her when it comes to men. I mean, look at my friend, for crissake. Oh, you went to school with him didn't you? You're probably friends or something", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Well, either you are or you aren't. Which is it", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Doing what", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Nothing", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I just want to ask you questions", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I just want to ask you questions", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "That's all", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "My first sexual experience or the first time I had intercourse", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Describe for me your first sexual experience", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Your first sexual experience", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "When I was fourteen", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Very much live", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "He just asked me questions", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Questions about sex", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Did he ask you to take your clothes off", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Did you take your clothes off", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "my friend, who knows where that tape may end up? He could be...bouncing it off some satellite or something. Some horny old men in that place or something could be watching it", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "You don't know that for sure", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Well, what the hell am I supposed to do", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "I can't believe you're doing this after I let you tape me", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "my friend, I don't know", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "I'm sorry. I can't do it", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "I was just saying, you know? I didn't get paranoid when you didn't want to make love. I could have easily assumed that you didn't want to because you were having an affair", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "I'm not either!", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "I like the way he dresses", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "\"The wrong hand", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Right", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "Doesn't work. He has to know the people, he has to be able to interact with them", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "You realize you have no recourse legally? This stuff could show up anywhere", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": " You trust him", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "It won't. I trust him", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "Yeah, I do. A helluva lot more than I trust you", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "my friend, we have nothing to talk about", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "No, my friend, things are getting real simple", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": " my friend and my friend have been...", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": " You know", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "What difference does it make why I do it", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "What would you know about a normal frame of mind", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "Hi, my friend", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "What tapes", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "Where are the tapes, my friend", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "You know which tapes! Where are they", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "What tapes", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "my friend, as a lawyer, you should know that those tapes are private property", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": " Why", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": " You're not like your sister. You couldn't be like her if you wanted to", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": " Have you fantasized about me", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": " I remember. You could do that, couldn't you? Go down on me", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": "So what happened? Was it so bad that it turned you off", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "What was the problem", "qsentId": 82}, {"answer": "Not yet. I'm not sure I will. I just want out", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 85, "question": "I don't know. It all gets back to that my friend thing. I don't like her...eagerness. There's nothing left to imagine, there's no..", "qsentId": 84}, {"answer": "You're not answering me", "docId": "sex_lies_and_video_tapes.txt", "asentId": 87, "question": "I want to know why you are the way you are", "qsentId": 86}]